[
  {
    "question": "Does it allow for expandable sd card??",
    "answer": "I just got my Samsung Galaxy S20 FE 5G and I can confirm without a doubt that there IS a slot for a microSD card! The people thumbing down that response are not paying attention. When you pull out the sim tray, there is a \"platform\" on the top labeled \"sim card 1\". You place your sim on that tray. UNDERNEATH is ANOTHER TRAY! You just turn the tray OVER and the other side says, \"sim card 2/microSD card\". You put another sim or your microSD card on THAT. Make sure you have the right size SD card, and/or you're putting it in correctly, for those complaining that it doesn't fit. You have to position it a certain way. Unfortunately, I'm using my phone to answer, so I can't show you in a video, but I was able to figure it out by myself. There ARE videos on YouTube, so just Google how to input your microSD for this device, if you want. (It should be common sense, especially with Google, and yet so many people never research anything prior to buying something, and then complain that they bought a device because it said it has a microSD card, and it doesn't). I just lined up the notches of the microSD card (the way the card is cut) with the notches of the tray, and voila! Now I'm off to buy a bigger microSD card (because I know I can!) ;) Good luck!"
  },
  {
    "question": "No headphone jack?  says it comes with akg headset.  is that wireless?",
    "answer": "The Samsung S21 FE continues the incredibly stupid design decision to remove a 3.5 mm headphone jack.  Unfortunately, most other competitive phones have done the same thing, so you've got to either go with a dongle (which risks breaking the USB-C port on the phone), or deal with all the hassles and low-fidelity of bluetooth buds.   Lord help you if one of those falls out of your ear while you're on the subway - there goes $100+."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will this work on T Mobile 5 G?",
    "answer": "Yes - T-Mobile 5g is focused on fr1 also known as Sub-6 (ghz) - this means you can take advantage of their 600mhz paint the map 5g (which is the slowest but offers other actual usable benefits) but also supports mid-band, which t-mo has tons of spectrum in (PCS & AWS) there's also speculation that BRS acquired from sprint could be later added (higher frequency equals faster data rates at the cost of shrinking coverage)... This does not support mmwave (aka ultrawideband) offered by VZW - but, that's basically useless anyway as you can't leave the line of site to a tower and maintain a connection at mmwave 5g anyway and at present the only sub 6 band they are deploying is 3.5ghz which doesn't provide the same coverage as lower bands... ATT is playing both ends but tmo has the most functional 5g nationally as of the time of my writing this... Keep in mind, 5g sub 6 is not multi gig speeds like you might think... Faster than 4g lte but more efficient which means more capacity and more throughput per user... In urban areas, with adequate spectrum, I've seen speeds over 500mbps... Not sure about the references to a special firmware build needed for this phone - saw a comment here for the first time about that - but it doesn't make sense... You should notify t-mo of your upgrade, sometimes an updated sim is needed to take advantage of latest 5g 600mhz band they offer..."
  },
  {
    "question": "The specs state it has 8gb of ram, but i thought the us model only had 6gb? does it only have 6gb of ram?",
    "answer": "I bought this because of the 8gb ram - if it's wrong why don't they fix it!!!\rThis is called misrepresentation and false advertisement. \rI was debating the 256gb phone but since it has a micro SD I chose not too . Had I known it had more ram I would have gotten that one."
  },
  {
    "question": "is this dual hybrid sim?",
    "answer": "This is supposed to be the US model, which is NOT dual SIM. In addition, the entire S20 series got eSIM functionality disabled on the US models, so no eSIM either. Google \"S20 USA eSIM\" for some pretty old forum threads complaining about that. Be aware of this and don't count on this feature."
  },
  {
    "question": "How easy is it to open the case and insert an SD card?",
    "answer": "Insert a paper clip into the top of the phone and the tray ejects out of the phone.\rTop slot is the sim card, bottom slot is the micro SD card slot.\r This phone does not have a rear removable cover. (Can't open the case)."
  },
  {
    "question": "Funciona en honduras , Con la la telefonia tigo ?",
    "answer": "Si, si funciona y perfectamente al 100%, yo acabo de adquirir este y soy de Honduras y me funciona muy bien y con Tigo."
  },
  {
    "question": "My phone came without an adapter, how will I charge it",
    "answer": "Strange. S20 FE comes with adapter in the box."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will my s7 sim card work?",
    "answer": "Yes, both S7 and S20 use the same size SIM card. As a matter of fact, just today, I upgraded my wife's old S7 to S20 FE and moved the SIM card from the old to the new card. The only reason why SIM card may be incompatible is if it is a larger size, but for that your old phone should be very old."
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this 6 gb or 8 gb ram?",
    "answer": "6gb"
  },
  {
    "question": "Headphone jack????",
    "answer": "Hi Cindy. Yes, the phone has a headphone jack. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this prepaid? I\u2019m sending this to my daughter and I want to know if she can take it out of the box and make a phone call.",
    "answer": "\u201cHi John, please be informed that this is a prepaid Tracfone Smartphone. ^Loejie\u201d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does it have Bluetooth, and picture in picture ?",
    "answer": "Hi Valued Customer. Yes, the phone has Bluetooth and can take pictures. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does this phone not have a message or call indicater light?",
    "answer": "I have a different model of Blu phone and it also does not have an indicator light. Apparently, that's how Blu phones are. :-/\rMy model also does not have camera stabilization, and I was buying this for the camera quality that was reported. The camera is nice just very hard to get the precise clarity I was anticipating.\r This phone is also a lot like using a Chromebook. It relief on all the Google -related apps to store you info, like photos and files go to Google photos and Google drive, not a gallery and download file folder."
  },
  {
    "question": "I live in arizona, but i want a pennsylvania phone number on this phone.  does it let me assign what area code i want?",
    "answer": "Hi Sherry. The system will generate a new phone number based with the zip code where you\u2019ll be using the phone the most, basically we\u2019re unable to use a Pennsylvania zip code in your current state which is Arizona. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this work great",
    "answer": "Hi Nathan. We are pleased to inform you that this phone works great since it is one of our 4G VoLTE supported devices. ^Monique"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this phone compatible with an otg cable?  i'm hoping to use it for a home brew vr helmet with an external camera for pass through.",
    "answer": "Hi Pete. I\u2019m sorry but your phone is compatible with OTG. ^Mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "I already have a tracfone can i use my current sim card ?",
    "answer": "Hi Cynthia. I\u2019m very sorry you can\u2019t use your old sim card in this device, because it will not work. This phone comes with a sim card already, if you wish to transfer your number and minutes we can process the transfer. Please call our customer care, if you already have this device. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we use the 90 day plan cards with this phone?",
    "answer": "Hi John. We are pleased to inform you that you can add a TracFone 90-day Plan airtime card. ^Monique"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will this phone work with the SIM card from my",
    "answer": "\u201cHi Kenneth, please be informed that this phone has its own pre-installed SIM card therefore it will only work with Tracfone program SIM card. ^Loejie\u201d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this work with mint mobile 5g?",
    "answer": "Right now there is no exact answer.  As I understand it Mint is an MVNO that uses T-Mobile towers where 5 g is available in specific limited areas.  T-Mobile is expanding its 5 g coverage but my information is that the OnePlus Nord 10 5g will work with the middle band.  5g has a low range and a high range band which are developmental in a word and it may be some time before there is a global availability.  There are problems with physical obstacles, etc. that affect reception that need to be overcome.  And there may not be an advantage over current LTE.  I would pay attention to how good the phone is currently and the value vs. the cost and I think this is a very good phone for the money."
  },
  {
    "question": "For this phone, how many security and android upgrades will we get, for how long> how many months/years? TIA",
    "answer": "First, do not listen to the folks that have headaches from this phone. It is super smooth and have had no issues with it. I own two in my house and I was informed it is on android 10, it will get to android 12 and no more android upgrade versions and three years of security updates (2021, 2022, 2023). Hope this helps."
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the nord in name mean?",
    "answer": "It means \"north\" in French"
  },
  {
    "question": "Processer?",
    "answer": "Qualcomm snapdragon 690"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there any way i could get the imei number before i buy the phone so that i can check if it's compatible on metro pcs website?",
    "answer": "Yes it\u2019s compatible with metropcs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this phone work with Crecket",
    "answer": "Yes the OnePlus Nord line (all of them) are compatible with Cricket.  You need an UNLOCKED phone (but the one Amazon sells is unlocked, so okay) and Cricket will send you a SIM card to insert in the phone.  I ran my phone's IMEI number on Cricket's compatability page to make sure.  I like my phone, btw."
  },
  {
    "question": "Sera posible poner seevicio de metro pcs?",
    "answer": "Si es posible"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will this work on all US carriers",
    "answer": "Does not work with t mobile/sprint as of July 2021"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this a US model?",
    "answer": "YES, on Amazon it'll tell you right under the price up to (04/23/21) $299.99 (up from $279.99 5 days ago) that it's a US Version. Euro & Global version is currently about $284.99."
  },
  {
    "question": "Don't care about 5g it says that the be2026, works with verizon? also do you know if it will work with net10 verizon?",
    "answer": "Works with Verizon subscription at 5G. Works with NET10 at 4G LTE, just make sure the APN setting have designated the Verizon Network and not AT&T. MInt offers 5G service on the T-Mobile Network at comparable cost."
  },
  {
    "question": "Att does it work with att",
    "answer": "It works with ATT 4G network, but not 5G. If you live in an area with only 5G ATT coverage, your phone will not work. If you look on the OnePlus 9 product page under \"Check Carrier Compatibility,\" you can see that no ATT 5G bands are supported, only T-Mobile and Verizon."
  },
  {
    "question": "Two questions: can the alexa be disabled or does this phone come with alexa \"bloatware\"? also, does it come in original packaging with warp charge65t?",
    "answer": "Yes, you can remove Alexa (thank god...) and it came with the 65w Warp charger and cable."
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this have a headphone jack?",
    "answer": "No it does not."
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this sprint tnx compatible?",
    "answer": "The device is unlocked for any carrier. So this device will work with Sprint, T-Mobile, or any other phone carrier within the US. Hope this helps!"
  },
  {
    "question": "Compatible with Boost Mobile?",
    "answer": "I used H2O, which shared the same network with AT&T, the cellular data does not work. H2O works well with my other phones for cellular data, like apple, huawei, LG, and TCL."
  },
  {
    "question": "Its support verizon sim 4g?",
    "answer": "Yeah, but you'll  need to call Verizon to get text working."
  },
  {
    "question": "Does wifi calling work for this phone on mint mobile in the usa?",
    "answer": "Supposed to"
  },
  {
    "question": "works with metropcs?",
    "answer": "Thank you for reaching out!\r Yes this is compatible with MetroPCS, T-Mobile, Verizon, AT&T, and Cricket"
  },
  {
    "question": "Cuales son las bandas que soporta?",
    "answer": "Hasta 5G"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this work on Mint's network?  4g?  5g?",
    "answer": "It will not work in 5G for ATT, it will only connect at 4G for ATT."
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this work internationally?",
    "answer": "Does this work at gsm 900 band( In Bangladesh)"
  },
  {
    "question": "At&t - will this device work with at & t's new 4g  sims as also post feb 2022 (when they shut down 3g) ? thanks",
    "answer": "full \"4g\" compatible. why i got it loaded with features, best value"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does your phone support 5g and is it dual sim? both sims support 5g?",
    "answer": "No 5G only 4G lite, but it does have dual sims."
  },
  {
    "question": "Do we have to use the 180 day service? Is it a no contract? Can I just put my sim card in and use my service?",
    "answer": "Mine was purchased Unlocked, so there was no contract or provider attached.  I would imagine this would depend on the individual phone purchase."
  },
  {
    "question": "How does the \"180-day cellular service included\" work? will instructions about this be included with the phone?",
    "answer": "Read the enclosed literature...not in everyatket or country"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do i get my 6 months free service from t mobile",
    "answer": "Speak to customer care service"
  },
  {
    "question": "Made in china?",
    "answer": "Yes, the Nokia G10 is manufactured in China.\r Thank you\r Customer support @ phonesnbeyond"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will it work with at&t after the Feb 3g shut down?",
    "answer": "Yes, it will! Thanks for your question."
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this phone compatible for safelink on at&t towers?",
    "answer": "Yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Funciona en mexico",
    "answer": "Si funciona aqu\u00ed en M\u00e9xico."
  },
  {
    "question": "Headphone jack????",
    "answer": "Hi Cindy. Yes, the phone has a headphone jack. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this prepaid? I\u2019m sending this to my daughter and I want to know if she can take it out of the box and make a phone call.",
    "answer": "\u201cHi John, please be informed that this is a prepaid Tracfone Smartphone. ^Loejie\u201d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does it have Bluetooth, and picture in picture ?",
    "answer": "Hi Valued Customer. Yes, the phone has Bluetooth and can take pictures. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does this phone not have a message or call indicater light?",
    "answer": "I have a different model of Blu phone and it also does not have an indicator light. Apparently, that's how Blu phones are. :-/\rMy model also does not have camera stabilization, and I was buying this for the camera quality that was reported. The camera is nice just very hard to get the precise clarity I was anticipating.\r This phone is also a lot like using a Chromebook. It relief on all the Google -related apps to store you info, like photos and files go to Google photos and Google drive, not a gallery and download file folder."
  },
  {
    "question": "I live in arizona, but i want a pennsylvania phone number on this phone.  does it let me assign what area code i want?",
    "answer": "Hi Sherry. The system will generate a new phone number based with the zip code where you\u2019ll be using the phone the most, basically we\u2019re unable to use a Pennsylvania zip code in your current state which is Arizona. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this work great",
    "answer": "Hi Nathan. We are pleased to inform you that this phone works great since it is one of our 4G VoLTE supported devices. ^Monique"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this phone compatible with an otg cable?  i'm hoping to use it for a home brew vr helmet with an external camera for pass through.",
    "answer": "Hi Pete. I\u2019m sorry but your phone is compatible with OTG. ^Mark"
  },
  {
    "question": "I already have a tracfone can i use my current sim card ?",
    "answer": "Hi Cynthia. I\u2019m very sorry you can\u2019t use your old sim card in this device, because it will not work. This phone comes with a sim card already, if you wish to transfer your number and minutes we can process the transfer. Please call our customer care, if you already have this device. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can we use the 90 day plan cards with this phone?",
    "answer": "Hi John. We are pleased to inform you that you can add a TracFone 90-day Plan airtime card. ^Monique"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will this phone work with the SIM card from my",
    "answer": "\u201cHi Kenneth, please be informed that this phone has its own pre-installed SIM card therefore it will only work with Tracfone program SIM card. ^Loejie\u201d"
  },
  {
    "question": "what is the largest and best sd card for moto g7 fast 2020 ??",
    "answer": "It's compatible with memory cards up to 512GB of memory. I bought this Micro SD Card > https://topreviews24..com/micro-sd-card/sandisk-extreme-micro/ < It's very fast!"
  },
  {
    "question": "how do you connect this to att? on the att website it does not list it as a supported phone.",
    "answer": "I love when companies do this. It's merely to trick you into not purchasing unlocked phones and purchase there phones. Now while some phones that are unlock have there share of trouble connecting to AT&T network, ultimately once you install your AT&T Sim card into the phone and restart phone it'll connect. I've been doing this with all kinds of phones and I've been with AT&T throughout 3 company name changes."
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this phone work with Straight Talk?",
    "answer": "Yes it does very well"
  },
  {
    "question": "Appears to ship with Android 10 - please verify?  How many version upgrades are guaranteed?",
    "answer": "my g7 optimo still gets upgrades. they just are not as fast as others getting them out. i do have to retire it at the end of the year however. they sent the message my phone is not votle ready and wont work in 2021. so maybe the one will be its replacement."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will the moto g fast work on us cellular?",
    "answer": "Yes it will. I bought one a few weeks ago. I'm on att in California and I'm making this post using mobile data. It's been my only phone since I unboxed."
  },
  {
    "question": "Do I have to use fingerprint sensor?",
    "answer": "No you can use pin pattern. None any of those options . \ud83e\udd18"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this phone compatible with Visible Wireless?",
    "answer": "While the phone is compatible, when you go to their website and type in the IMEI number, it will tell you it will not work.\rIt will work, I have one on Visible. I ran into this issue when Motorola first introduced the G power, I bought one from Motorola, \rwhen I typed in the IMEI on Visible, it said it would not work, so I bought the Pixel 4a.\rNow, a few months later, visible sells the G power, and when I type in my IMEI, it says, my phone will work! So I have a stand by spare!\rBy the way, I took the sim card out of my Pixel and put it in the G fast, and it works fine. The problem is, if your IMEI says it won't work, they will not send you a sim card."
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this phone have a warranty?",
    "answer": "1 year parts and labor. Warranties are only valid in the country of which the phone is  intended for use.  The warranty here will be only honored in  the US."
  },
  {
    "question": "Will this phone work on visible?",
    "answer": "Visible wireless is an MVNO which uses the Verizon network.  If you visit the Motorola corporate  website it will state that the Moto G Fast (2020)is compatible with Verizon MVNO's  supporting VoLTE."
  },
  {
    "question": "Phone works great, but i am only receiving some of my texts messages; my old moto e4 plus phone is still receiving texts. why?",
    "answer": "Check with you service provider. Also if you have a same company's SIM card in both phone.... that's maybe your issues."
  },
  {
    "question": "Description says this is a 5g but other questions that were answered says it is a 4g. which exactly is this phone? i need 4g. thanks",
    "answer": "There are two different models in this listing. One is the 4G 2021 model, the other is the 5G 2022 model. You have to click on which one you want to order."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can these be activated with Verizon? If so, would there be any limitations?",
    "answer": "Hi Kelly. Yes, the phone can be activated with Verizon as long as you unlocked it on TraFone. There is no limitation on it. ^Rogie"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tracfone: it comes with android 10, but how many version upgrades do we get? my moto g power (2020) updated to 11.",
    "answer": "Hi Eric. Please be advised that the software version of a device will depend on its manufacturer. Since you have a Motorola phone, the software version of your phone will depend with Motorola. ^Jacob"
  },
  {
    "question": "can this phone make wifi calls too?",
    "answer": "Hi valued customer. Please be informed that the phone in question is supported with WiFi calling. ^Anafe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this have a Usb type c?",
    "answer": "Hi Cathy M. Please be informed that the phone includes a USB-C charger. ^Rosemond"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have a moto x pure with tracfone sim. Can this newer model be ported over to my current account? Using new or old sim cards?",
    "answer": "Hi Robert, please be informed that you can port or transfer your service over to this phone and use the new SIM card which is already inserted to the device. ^Kosher"
  },
  {
    "question": "I have seen two answers.  Is this a 2000 or 2001 version?",
    "answer": "Hi Weeble. Please be informed that the phone in question is the latest G Stylus phone with 128GB which is a 2021 version. ^Kathleen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Does this phone have fingerprint security?",
    "answer": "Hi Willie L. Yes, the phone in question have finger security. ^Kathleen"
  },
  {
    "question": "is this a front and rear facing camera?",
    "answer": "Dear valued customer, we are pleased to inform you that this phone will indeed have both a front (16 MP) and rear camera (48 MP - wide, 16 MP - ultra wide and 2 MP - macro). ^Arjay"
  },
  {
    "question": "When this phone isrefilled with tracfone prepaid card,  are the minutes tripled like my samsung galaxy j7 crown?",
    "answer": "Hi Orlando R. Fuller. Please be informed that the phone in question does not have a Triple Minute Plan benefits. However, if you have an old device with Triple Minute Plan benefits and you will transfer to the new phone the benefits will also be transferred. ^Kathleen"
  },
  {
    "question": "does this phone display minutes and days remaining on the face page?",
    "answer": "Hi Maggie. Unfortunately, the remaining balance (talk, text, data and service days) will not display on the phone\u2019s screen. In order to check the balance, you will need to text the keyword \u201cBALANCE\u201d or numerical code \u201c411\u201d to short code 611611. ^Marvin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can i play roblox and youtube on it without a sim card",
    "answer": "Hi Daiseuna. Yes, you can play Roblox and YouTube without a sim card. You can connect to a Wi-Fi for internet connection. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "can i set this phone up and get it working from home  my current tracfone is obsolete and will no longer work?",
    "answer": "Hi Valued Customer. Yes. You can definitely transfer your current TracFone phone number and account to this new phone. You use our website (www.tracfone.com), or you may text the keyword \u201cUPGRADE\u201d to 611611 to process the transfer. You may also contact us at 1-800-867-7183 if you need assistance. For your convenience, our representatives are available Monday-Sunday from 8:00 AM to 11:45 PM EST. ^Jesel"
  },
  {
    "question": "HI, I just want to use this with my home wifi only for calling apps and streaming shows from the web. do i need anything extra?",
    "answer": "Hi Valued Customer. Yes, you can use this phone for calling using an app and streaming videos. You don\u2019t need to pay extra. ^Christian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can this phone be activated with safelink?",
    "answer": "Hi KennethBWilgus. We are pleased to inform you that you can use or activate this phone with SafeLink Wireless. ^Monique"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you buy minutes and use them until they're used up or do you need to pay monthly?",
    "answer": "You can buy minutes at any time if you buy a minutes plan. Unused minutes, data and texts roll over past the date. The date is also added on; for example, if you buy the $25 plan for 500 minutes, 500 texts and 500 mb data and sixty days to use them, if you don't use them in that sixty days, it rolls over until the sixty days expires. If you buy another $25 plan say, after 30 days on this plan, your 30 left over days plus 60 new days then bumps you out to 90 days, PLUS whatever minutes, data and texts you have left are added to the new purchase.\r  UNLESS, you buy an unlimited plan for $25 which is for one month only. Which you do not need to do. You can also pay the $125 for a whole year and get 2,000 minutes and 365 days to use them, plus GB of data and thousands of texts. Sometimes this plan goes on sale for $75 and it's a bargain."
  },
  {
    "question": "Does it maps and travel directions gps?",
    "answer": "Hi Joan E Blue. Please be informed that the phone in question is compatible with GPS. ^Anafe"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you FaceTime on this phone?",
    "answer": "\u201cHi Amazon Customer, please be informed that this phone does not support Facetime because it is an Android phone not an Iphone. ^Loejie\u201d"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do trac fone card sold in local stores work to add minutes  like the old flip phones?",
    "answer": "Hi J. Please be advised that if you old phone is no longer supported with our upgraded network, our TracFone plans can no longer be added to it. ^Monique"
  },
  {
    "question": "will it work with page plus",
    "answer": "Hi JB. Please be informed that the phone in question will not work with Page Plus Cellular. ^Kathleen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can i transfer myself  or do i need a  tech",
    "answer": "Hi Carolyn. Please be informed that you can transfer your service and phone number from one device to another. You may text the keyword \u201cTransfer\u201d to 611611. ^Kathleen"
  },
  {
    "question": "can I keep my current tracfone  number I had for 10 yrs and my minutes?",
    "answer": "Hi Dougie. Yes, you can keep your phone number as long as it is still active or available. ^Kathleen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is it cdma or gsm?  this information is necessary.",
    "answer": "Hi Pro Diver. Please be informed that the phone in question is a CDMA phone. ^Kathleen"
  },
  {
    "question": "If i purchase, & i use safelink wireless (which is affiliated with tracphone), can i retain my current phone number on the switch over?",
    "answer": "Hi Chuck. Yes, you can keep your phone number to activate the new phone. ^Kathleen"
  },
  {
    "question": "What version of bluetooth does this have?",
    "answer": "Hi Shannon, this phone has a Bluetooth specification of 5.1, A2DP, LE. ^Arjay"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is dual sims",
    "answer": "Hi Valued Customer. Thank you for your interest in our product. We regret to inform you that this item in question does not have dual SIM. ^Jacob"
  },
  {
    "question": "I bought this phone and it does not say it is a cdma phone anywhere. Not on the box or on the phone. Where is it listed that it is cdma?",
    "answer": "Good day Valued Customer. Please be advised that the phone`s technology is 4G VoLTE CDMA. ^Monique"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can it charge wirelessly",
    "answer": "Hi Cinder. Please be informed that the phone in question is not compatible with wireless charger. ^Anafe"
  },
  {
    "question": "It connects to allow data flow but at the same time, the network is unavailable for calls and texts? Wtf?!",
    "answer": "We had the same problem and had to do a factory reset and it works fine now"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do you have to buy cards to put minutes on the phone or do they have monthly options on the phone",
    "answer": "Steer clear of Tracfone!!!!!!!!\r I had them for years. No problems then Verizon bought them out. They cut off both my New BLU view 3 phones. Couldn't make calls on either one. NO SERVICE. So it looks like verizon cut off a lot of customers that had carry over. I had 10gigs data of carry over along with minutes & TEXT DATA in the thousands. GONE!!  Spent days & days calling TRACFONE no help! \rLove the phone hate the carrier. Never going back. Got new unlocked phones and went with Mint T-Mobile. LOVE THEM they know what service is all about."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you set up an Alexa with this phone",
    "answer": "Hello Katerya, to answer it short, yes. In order to use the TracFone Alexa skill, you first need to enable it just search \u201cTracFone\u201d in the Alexa App or from Alexa skills store on Amazon.com. You can also say, \u201cEnable TracFone skill.\u201d After enabling the skill, all you have for you to do, is enter your TracFone phone number. It is that easy. ^Barry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Has anyone been able to find a case that fits this version of the phone? Suggestions welcome.",
    "answer": "It took me forever to find a case for the Revvlry Plus (Moto G7 Plus). This fit the oval lens perfect. No bulging and inexpensive. I wish it came in other colors (besides neon green and black). Amazon:  CasemartUSA Phone Case for [T-Mobile REVVLRY Plus (2019)], [Protech Series][Black] Shockproof Brushed Slim Impact Resistant Defender Cover for T-Mobile REVVLRY Plus (2019) . My son really likes it. It was going to be a temporary case until he found something else, but it is nice looking and fits well, so it will be permanent."
  },
  {
    "question": "The us version is suppose to have volte, can some one confirm for sure?",
    "answer": "Yep, I have tmobile & volte is working."
  },
  {
    "question": "Now that Sprint and t-mobile have merged, will this phone work on a Sprint plan?",
    "answer": "This cellphone will work on the T-Mobile network but not on the Sprint network."
  },
  {
    "question": "Would it work in Ecuador?",
    "answer": "If you are traveling you can purchase a separate sim card. However, it's recommended not to buy a US based model if living outside the US as some features on the phone may not be available.  Motorola warranty are also only valid on phone in the region where they were intended to be sold."
  },
  {
    "question": "My order is delayed, phone case came days ago, waiting on the phone. Are these low in stock?",
    "answer": "Mine wasn't. Shipped immediately."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can i use this phone in the Philippines",
    "answer": "Thanks for your interest. All of our phones should work in countries that you may be traveling to. However, we cannot guarantee that all features will work seamlessly outside the US. Please check with your mobile service provider to see if your SIM is expected to operate. Please note that we never recommend buying a phone in one region for ongoing use in another as Motorola phones are only in warranty in the country/region in which they are intended for sale. - Mike"
  },
  {
    "question": "Silbe fuera de eeuu?",
    "answer": "S\u00ed, pero es un tel\u00e9fono hecho para los Estados Unidos, pero puedes usarlo para viajar.  Sin embargo, algunas caracter\u00edsticas y funcionalidades no est\u00e1n disponibles cuando se usan fuera de los Estados Unidos. Por lo general, si vives fuera de los Estados Unidos, es mejor comprar un tel\u00e9fono destinado a la regi\u00f3n donde vives.  Esta garant\u00eda del dispositivo solo se respetar\u00e1 si se presenta dentro de los EE. UU."
  },
  {
    "question": "can you use this for international travel with a european country local sim card ?",
    "answer": "The Moto G7 Plus (2019) phone will work Internationally with the purchase of a separate Sim card when traveling abroad.  Please keep in mind some features and functionality of the phone can be hindered if not used in the region where the phone was originally intended. This is a US based version of this phone. Please be aware the the warranty will be only honored here in the US."
  },
  {
    "question": "Can be used on any network? Metropcs etc?",
    "answer": "Please visit the Motorola corporate website.  In the search screen enter Moto G7 Plus  to bring up the phone. Scroll to  \"view all specification\" then scroll down to \"carrier compatible\"  to see the full listing."
  }
]